Hold him down here.
Go outside and keep watch.
Since we are allies,
we agreed to advance and retreat together.
Why did you take all the caning
upon yourself?
You
know no martial arts.
After ten strikes,
your body will be crippled.
Besides, this is the only way
to make them believe
that you are in my heart.
Chu Shengyi,
what kind of person are you?
Water.
I'll go get it.
I knew she didn't like you.
But no matter how much she dislikes you,
she raised you for so many years.
How could she be so cruel?
Xin'er's pain
is probably a hundred times
worse than this.
Today, I
also saw the wounds on Ye Xin.
Is everything arranged?
Rest assured.
I've already given her the medicine.
Ye Xin's act in the hall today
was so well coordinated.
It will definitely fool
the little prince of Quantan.
Good.
Momo,
why are you here?
Momo.
Master ordered that
no one is allowed near the study.
I am here on Madam's orders
to visit the Third Master.
Step aside.
The Young Master said
no one is to disturb him.
Third Master,
I am here on Madam's orders
to deliver medicine to you.
Let her in.
Higher.
Master, this is...
Do you
know your mistake?
I
know my mistake.
I shouldn't have contradicted Mother
and caused you to be punished.
If it weren't for
your cousin,
I would absolutely not
protect you today.
Thank you, Master.
Third Master,
Madam sent me
to check on your injuries.
I'm fine now.
Thank Mother for her concern.
Third Master,
don't hold a grudge against Madam.
I've served her for so many years,
and I know best
that her strictness towards you
is all for your own good.
This is the medicine Madam specially prepared for you.
Thank Mother.
Momo,
is there anything else?
Today is the Mid-Autumn Festival.
Yet you are so badly injured.
It seems I can't return to the manor.
Madam specifically asked
if you
have any message to take back.
Yes.
Thank Mother for her concern.
Making Mother
angry today
was all my fault.
Please tell Mother, Momo,
do not let my mistakes
ruin
the joy of family reunion.
What about the Commander-in-Chief?
If you have nothing else, Momo,
please go back first.
In that case,
I shall take my leave.
Come here.
I
made a mistake today
and deserve to be punished.
Momo has left.
You don't have to act anymore.
My lord, don't move.
Your wound will tear open again.
You don't blame me, do you?
This is the only way
to keep you safe.
Bear with it.
My mother's medicine
is useful for many kinds of wounds.
My lord, you are still injured.
I
will take my leave now.
Today is Mid-Autumn Festival.
I had Granny Lan make this specially.
Try it.
Eat slowly.
No one is fighting you for it.
So amazing.
Every Mid-Autumn Festival from now on,
I want to be with you, Mother.
Silly child.
How can I be with you for the rest of your life?
I don't care.
I'll go wherever you go.
We will always be together.
Okay.
Did you see clearly?
In this Governor's Mansion,
I've seen so many infatuated lovers.
I have helped you manage the household affairs
and observed for so many years.
I definitely wouldn't be wrong.
One is deeply in love but finds it hard to speak,
the other is secretly in love but dares not say.
They are exactly like a pair of
ill-fated lovers from an opera.
To think he would defy me for a lowly girl.
Madam,
be careful with your hands.
Don't hurt yourself.
It's my fault.
For so many years,
I've been so focused on watching Ye Xin, this chess piece,
that I let someone else take advantage of the situation.
Next,
what should we do?
Madam,
this was sent from the posthouse.
Step down.
Yes.
Lady Ye has contracted an epidemic.
She wants to move out of the posthouse.
The young prince specifically asks for your opinion, Madam.
Just a useless chess piece.
It's his own plaything.
Let him deal with it himself.
Yes.
Your Highness.
I know I don't have much time left.
According to Kuizhou law,
those with severe illnesses can be divorced.
I beg Your Highness to show mercy
and let me return to my hometown.
If Your Highness does not agree,
I will kill myself right here.
Although my father died on the battlefield,
if I really die in this Quantan posthouse,
his old friends in the army
will definitely not let this go.
Your Highness,
An epidemic is an ominous sign.
I'm afraid it will clash with trade.
Since Lady Li has already spoken,
How about...
Get lost.
Hya!
Farewell, young prince.
Xin'er is here
to thank you both for saving my life. Please, get up.
Please, get up.
I saved you for my own reasons.
You don't need to take it to heart.
My lady, you risked your life for me
without regard for your own,
and even protected the business.
You didn't harm anyone for my sake.
With such great kindness,
you truly deserve this respect.
Take your time talking.
I'll go keep watch for you.
All these years,
for my sake,
you've suffered.
No.
It was me.
I failed to keep my promise
and protect you.
We were just children then.
There was nothing we could do.
It was just fate.
Do you have to go?
If you're looking for a shelter,
maybe I can help.
Shengyi,
all these years,
I've never lived for myself.
When I was young, for my father,
I entered the Commander's mansion as a hostage.
Later, Madam Li
gave me to the little prince.
All my life,
I've always been pushed around by others.
I even
never thought about
what I was really living for.
Now I'm finally free.
I want to,
I want to truly live for myself for once.
The bracelet,
I fixed it.
Shengyi,
you will always be my family,
my most important younger brother.
From now on,
you are Chu Shengyi's only family.
If Madam Li ever makes things difficult for you,
even if it costs me my life,
I will protect you.
Okay.
We are family for life.
Take care.
Okay.
Let's go, Xin'er.
After Mother left,
in this vast Commander's mansion,
only you truly protected me.
This debt of gratitude is as heavy as a mountain,
I will remember it for the rest of my life.
No matter where you are,
you will always be my most important
family.